Zeus Cordeiro

Tampa, Florida, United States



zeus.cordeiro@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/zeus-cordeiro



https://zcordeiro.github.io/Zeus-Cordeiro-portfolio/

Summary

I have close to ten years of management experience in hospitality, and am now breaking into a new field of software development. I've been working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind, and more. I am seeking a position where I can apply the knowledge I've already gained and continue to learn more in this ever changing industry.

Experience



Bartender

Cigar City Brewing

Feb 2012 - Aug 2014 (2 years 7 months)

Responsible for maintaining a clean and organized space for guests to enjoy as well as ensuring guest experience was exceptional to assure the brewery tasting room maintained a very steady stream of regular clients.

Tasting Room General Manager

Coppertail Brewing Co

Aug 2014 - Oct 2022 (8 years 3 months)

I was hired at Coppertail Brewing in 2014 as the Tasting Room General Manager, I oversaw the build out of our two floor 5,500 square foot tasting room. I supervised 7 managers and over 60 other staff members in the years I spent there. I managed multiple yearly large scale events. I maintained steady profits year after year in my department and built a steady client base in that time.

Education



University of Central Florida

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, Computer Software Engineering 2022 - 2023

Skills

Leadership • Communication • Collaborative Problem Solving • Budget Management • Training • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • jQuery • Bootstrap